JGSM Audio-Visual Collection /4303 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
JGSM Audio-Visual Collection
1984-1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Johnson Graduate School of Management
/4303 AV
1.44 cubic feet
1.4 linear ft.
Audiovisual material.
JGSM audio recordings of symposiums, lectures, ralls, retirement celebrations and Council-Trustee weekend.
8232603
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 06, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6174/001: NYSUT President's Office Files
Johnson Graduate School of Management (Cornell University)
8232603
- Tech Symposium - 4/9/1999 - Luncheon Speaker - Jim Long, 1 (Box 1)
- Tech Symposium - 4/9/1999 -- Preparing for the net generation - Moderator - Ainsley, 2 (Box 1)
- 141 Tape two - Qued to 1st presentation, 3 (Box 1)
- 141 tape three - Qued to 1st presentation, 4 (Box 1)
- 141 tape one - Qued to 1st presentation, 5 (Box 1)
- Tech Symposium - 4/9/1999 - Starting up success - Moderator - Ben Daniel, 6 (Box 1)
- Tech Symposium - 4/9/1999 - Dean Swieringa - Opening Speaker - W. Schrader, 7 (Box 1)
- David Bechhofer, Bain & Company - 10/3/1998 - Case Discussion "Copeland", 8 (Box 1)
- Dean - Robert Ryan - Opening Speaker, 9 (Box 1)
- Tech Symposium - 4/9/1999 -- Conclusion, 10 (Box 1)
- Tech Symposium - 4/9/1999 - Financial Services - Moderator - S. Tasker, 11 (Box 1)
- Tech Mgmt. Symposium - Dan Hesse - 4/8/1998, 12 (Box 1)
- Dinland Lecture - 4/1/1998 - Dennis Dammerman, 13 (Box 1)
- Wake up on Wallstreet - 4/5/1999, 4/12/1999, 4/19/1999, 14 (Box 1)
- Terry Stewart, Pres. Marvel Entertainment Group, Inc. - 6/11/1994 -- Reunion address "Do What You Love"; "Love What You Do: the Key to Success", 15 (Box 1)
- Wall Street Wake-Up Calls - 3/1-Competition & the NYSE Specialist; 3/8-Global-Exchange.com?; 3/15-Circuit Breakers + Trading Holts, 16 (Box 1)
- The Scientist as Manager: Emergence of a New Business Elite? - A Johnson School Roundtable, Oct. 18, 1995, 17 (Box 1)
- JGSM Follies 1986, 18 (Box 1)
- The Scientist as Manager: Emergence of a new business elite?; Johnson School Roundtable, Oct. 18, 1995, 19 (Box 1)
- Atkinson (Market Timing), 20 (Box 1)
- Tech Symposium - 4/9/1999 - Internet New Media - Moderator - Stayman, 21 (Box 1)
- B-09 tape two - Qued to 1st presentation, 22 (Box 1)
- B-09 - tape 1 - Qued to 1st presentation, 23 (Box 1)
- Dean David Thomas Retirement - 5/25/1984, 24 (Box 1)
- Cornell's Johnson School Rally - 1/30/1997 (Box 2)
- Cornell's Johnson School Rally - 1/30/1997 (Box 3)
- Council-Trustee Weekend Highlights (Box 4)
- Council-Trustee Weekend Highlights, 1984 (Box 5)